<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs on ZFS Snap Diff</title><link>https://j-keck.github.io/zfs-snap-diff/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Docs on ZFS Snap Diff</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://j-keck.github.io/zfs-snap-diff/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Installation</title><link>https://j-keck.github.io/zfs-snap-diff/docs/install/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-keck.github.io/zfs-snap-diff/docs/install/</guid><description>This describes the currently unreleased beta version. Binary packages You can download the latest binary package from here or from the githup release page.
Linux Download the beta version for Linux amd64 here:
zfs-snap-diff-linux-v1.0.0-beta-16-g1bae2c4.tgz
FreeBSD Download the beta version for FreeBSD amd64 here:
zfs-snap-diff-freebsd-v1.0.0-beta-16-g1bae2c4.tgz
macOS Download the beta version for macOS amd64 here:
zfs-snap-diff-darwin-v1.0.0-beta-16-g1bae2c4.tgz
Solaris Download the beta version for Solaris amd64 here:</description></item><item><title>zfs-snap-diff</title><link>https://j-keck.github.io/zfs-snap-diff/docs/zfs-snap-diff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-keck.github.io/zfs-snap-diff/docs/zfs-snap-diff/</guid><description>This describes the currently unreleased beta version. zfs-snap-diff - web application to find older versions of a given file in your zfs snapshots.
With zfs-snap-diff you can
find older file versions in your zfs-snapshots for a given file
view the file content from a given snapshot
inspect a diff from the older version to the actual version
revert a single change</description></item><item><title>zsd</title><link>https://j-keck.github.io/zfs-snap-diff/docs/zsd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-keck.github.io/zfs-snap-diff/docs/zsd/</guid><description>This describes the currently unreleased beta version. zsd - cli tool to find older versions of a given file in your zfs snapshots.
With zsd you can
find older file versions in your zfs snapshots for a given file
view the file content from a given snapshot
inspect a diff from the older version to the actual version
restore a version from a zfs snapshot</description></item><item><title>Changelog</title><link>https://j-keck.github.io/zfs-snap-diff/docs/changelog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-keck.github.io/zfs-snap-diff/docs/changelog/</guid><description>1.0.0-beta (unreleased) This version is a complete rewrite.
The backend is implemented in Go (as before) and the frontend in PureScript.
create and destroy snapshots from the webapp
download a complete directory as a zip-archive
zsd cli tool to find different file-versions in the command line
does not need a running zfs-snap-diff instance date-range based search for file versions</description></item></channel></rss>